{
    "id": "d35ee6d63c174bec9339ebca65d66461",
    "title": "First Conditional Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If he doesn’t mend his ways, he ………………… in serious trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will land",
                "would land",
                "would have landed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "31d6ab70c722443e812083e49a20c916"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. hard you will pass the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "worked",
                "had worked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "273e65e494ff499a99a84433e7bc38af"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he ………………….. now, we can all have dinner together.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "arrives",
                "arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f539ff501ce490b8880405df16829f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………… her, she will not come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't invite",
                "don't invite",
                "hadn't invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1bc8de92692240aab70e683ce1f389f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I don’t meet him, I ………………….. to his mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will talk",
                "would talk",
                "would have talked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "487101b58dbd4794aad1523097e6da57"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she ………………. English, she will get a better job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "speaks",
                "had spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5dea3fcd8b414638ba547baa5c31fc02"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he arrives now, we ....................... in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would be",
                "will be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f56b528503e3468c945f310cf47869f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she ………………… out the truth, she will be really angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "finds",
                "found"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72dc8e7df82b4a46996b365ead0565dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ……………… a millionaire, I will not work at all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9de5156886ab4dc3ab9c88cc9d9526ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ………………… the answer, I will tell you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knows",
                "know",
                "knew"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f9871d4059d4ee8b1bc8a7655f47387"
        }
    ]
}